[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "courseID": 1,
        "date": "2/28/24",
        "question": "Is this a question?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "This is an answer to your question.",
                "helpful": 4,
                "unhelpful": 1
            }
        ]

    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "courseID": 2,
        "date": "3/17/20",
        "question": "Are there programming assignments?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "yes, there are two of them.",
                "helpful": 4,
                "unhelpful": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "courseID": 3,
        "date": "5/2/24",
        "question": "Is this a difficult course?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "No, it was fairly easy. I'd recommend it",
                "helpful": 4,
                "unhelpful": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "courseID": 4,
        "date": "12/12/23",
        "question": "Is there a lot of reading?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Yes",
                "helpful": 4,
                "unhelpful": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "courseID": 5,
        "date": "7/8/22",
        "question": "Is this class worth taking?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Yes! In my opinion it was a really interesting class that you'll learn a lot from.",
                "helpful": 4,
                "unhelpful": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "courseID": 6,
        "date": "9/2/23",
        "question": "Are there essays and are they graded hard?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "There were two essays when I took it, but they weren't too difficult. The professor wasn't a super harsh grader either.",
                "helpful": 4,
                "unhelpful": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "courseID": 7,
        "date": "1/2/22",
        "question": "How difficult is this class?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "This was a really difficult course for me. You definitely shouldn't take it unless required to or you really like physics.",
                "helpful": 4,
                "unhelpful": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "courseID": 8,
        "date": "2/15/24",
        "question": "Would you recommend this class?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "I'd only recommend it for those who love physics/science as it can be difficult and a lot of work.",
                "helpful": 4,
                "unhelpful": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "courseID": 9,
        "date": "3/3/24",
        "question": "Should I take this at ISU or a community college?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "I took it at DMACC and it was really easy. I've heard it's really hard at ISU, so I'd recommend a community college.",
                "helpful": 4,
                "unhelpful": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "courseID": 10,
        "date": "5/3/24",
        "question": "How hard is this class?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "I actually found this easier than calc II, however, I wouldn't recommend it if you don't like math.",
                "helpful": 4,
                "unhelpful": 1
            }
        ]
    }
]
